Some women would kill for a baby
Inside is a horror, thriller film directed by Miguel Ángel Vivas.
Completely on her own, Sarah spends her time at home,
waiting for the approaching birth of her child.
But one night, a stranger breaks into her home, ready to
snatch her still unborn baby from her.
Sarah Clark, played by Rachel Nichols.
Madeleine Sherman, played by Laura Harring.
Isaac, played by Ben Temple.
Sarah's Mother, played by Gillian Apter.
Police Woman, played by Andrea Tivadar.
Police Officer 3, played by Craig Stevenson.
Inside is a 2016 English-language Spanish horror film directed Miguel Ángel Vivas,
who co-wrote the screenplay with Jaume Balagueró and Manu Díez.
It stars Rachel Nichols and Laura Harring.
The plot follows a pregnant woman pursued by a psychotic woman
trying to steal her unborn child on Christmas Eve.
It is a remake of the 2007 French film of the same name.
The film had its premiere on 7 October 2016 at the Sitges Film Festival.
The tone is dark and intense.